{
    "id": "46c495ab28044e518ed310c5c2aca269",
    "title": "Simple Present Or Present Continuous",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ………………….. a great time on this holiday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "am having"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She is Italian. She ………………… from Milan.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "comes",
                "is coming"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ................................ TV at the moment.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "watch",
                "am watching"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I .................................. to the mountains about twice a year.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "am going"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "My head ………………….....",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "aches",
                "is aching",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………….. what he says.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do not believe",
                "am not believing"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Cows …………………. on grass.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "feed",
                "are feeding"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We …………………. to visit you next month.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "come",
                "are coming"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I will ring her up because I …………………… to talk.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "need",
                "am needing"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………… to go now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "want",
                "am wanting"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}